(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
尾丸ポルカです、お願いしまーす！
I'm Omaru Polka, pleased to meet you!
こんばんは、白上フブキです。よろしくお願いします！
Good evening, I'm Shirakami Fubuki. Nice to meet you!
さて、今夜も始まりました。『MUSIC GARDEN』でございますけれども。
Now then, tonight's show has begun. It's time for 'MUSIC GARDEN'.
始まっちゃったね。
It's started.
はい。
Yes.
髪切った？
Did you cut your hair?
髪はまだ切ってないですけど。
I haven't cut it yet...
これから切る予定？
...do you plan to?
そうですね。暑くなってきてますのでね。ちょっとばっさりいきたいなとは思っているんですけど。
Well, it's getting hotter, so I'm thinking of cutting it short.
そ。
I see.
そうなんです。髪切りましたよね、そういえば。
That's right. By the way, you cut yours, didn't you?
いや、切ってない。
No, I didn't.
切ってますよね。
You totally did.
いや、切らない。
No, I won't.
何か結構前に...
Quite a while ago...
それより今日は何か、ルイ君誕生...
More importantly, today is Lui-kun's birth...
そうですね。お誕生日ということで、めでたいですね。
That's right. It's her birthday, so it's a happy day.
髪切った？
Did she cut her hair?
髪は切ってないですけども。逆に切られましたよね。
She didn't, but her screen time got cut instead.
その時間じゃない。
It's not that kind of segment.
あ...まずは本日のゲストのご紹介です。
Ah... first, let me introduce today's guests.
はい。
Yes.
今夜も豪華ゲストでお送りする『MUSIC GARDEN』。
'MUSIC GARDEN', bringing you gorgeous guests tonight as well.
なんと今夜は話題の海外グループも中継で繋がってるそうですよ。
Tonight, we're even connecting with a popular overseas group via remote link!
最後まで見逃せません！
Don't miss a thing until the very end!
はい。もうこれ、鷹嶺ルイ君。
Right. And here's Takane Lui-kun.
すっかり常連だね。
She's practically a regular now.
あ、ありがとうございます。今日ちょっと1回目だと思うんですけど、ありがとうございます。
Ah, thank you. I think it's actually my first time, but thank you.
あ、今日で確か、あれ？白上君、61回目？
Ah, if I recall... Shirakami-kun, is this the 61st time?
そうですね。本日61回目になりますね。
That's right. Today marks the 61st episode.
Mガデは実は61回目 ルイと掛けてと思いきや...?
Actually the 61st episode of M-Gade. Just when you think it's a pun on Lui (6-1)...?
ルイと掛けてと思いきや...ありがとうございます。
I thought it was a pun on 'Lui' (6-1)... thank you.
Mガデ61回やってたんだ、この番組。
So M-Gade has been on for 61 episodes.
あ、なんか、すみませんなんか、私、自我を出してしまいました。本当すみません。
Ah, sorry, I ended up showing too much of my ego. Truly sorry.
ごめんなさい。
I'm sorry.
あ、61回出演してるもんね、君は。
Well, you've appeared 61 times after all.
61回も出演してました。あ、じゃあこれからもね、62回、63回と毎回お願いします。
I've appeared 61 times?! Ah, then please have me on every time from now—62, 63, and so on.
はい、じゃあということで。今夜もよろしくお願いします。
Right, with that said. Let's get started with tonight's show.
よろしくお願いします！
Please look forward to it!
それではミュージックガーデン、スタートです！
Well then, Music Garden, let's start!
最初のゲストは、鷹嶺ルイです！
Our first guest is Takane Lui!
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you!
鷹嶺ルイ
Takane Lui
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you!
誕生日！
Your birthday!
はい、ありがたいことに誕生日なんです。ありがとうございます。
Yes, thankfully it is my birthday. Thank you very much.
おめでとう！
Happy Birthday!
これ、最近もらった情報だと...
According to some info I got recently...
...悪夢を見て起きちゃうんだって？
...you wake up after having nightmares?
そうなんですよ、悪夢めちゃくちゃ見てて。
That's right, I've been having so many nightmares.
最近は悪夢をよく見る
Lately, she's often been having nightmares
例えばこのMガデの収録とかで...
For example, for the recording of this M-Gade...
...もう誰もいないとか。
...nobody is there.
あとライブ幕上がったら誰もいないとか。
And when the curtain rises for a live show, there's no one.
そういう悪夢を見て...
I have those kinds of nightmares...
...起きて泣くっていう。
...and wake up crying.
泣いてマネージャーに連絡するっていう、そういう感じですかね、最近は。
I cry and then contact my manager, that's how it's been lately.
マネージャーさんそれ、大変じゃないの？
Isn't that tough for your manager?
あの、起きてから連絡来ると...
Well, when I contact them after waking up...
...「よしよし」って連絡くれますね。
...they reply with "there, there."
マネージャーさんは君のお母さんか何か？
Is your manager your mother or something?
そう、なんかお母さんみたいにしてくれます。
Yeah, they treat me like a mother would.
え、ポルさんは悪夢とか見ますか？
Eh, do you have nightmares, Pol-san?
最近見ないな。
I haven't lately.
どういう夢見るんですか？
What kind of dreams do you have?
夢？ 覚えてないことが多いな。白上君？
Dreams? I usually don't remember. How about you, Shirakami-kun?
はい、夢はもちろん見ますよ。
Yes, of course I have dreams.
どんな夢？
What kind of dreams?
そうですね、最近見た夢ですと...
Let's see, a dream I had recently...
...山の中にいて...
...I was in the mountains...
...よく分からないキノコを採ってるという。
...and I was picking mysterious mushrooms.
白上君もよくわかんないね。
Shirakami-kun is also hard to understand.
ちょっと夢占い行きましょうか、一緒にね。
Let's go for a dream reading together.
夢占い！そうですね、ご一緒させていただければと思います。
Dream reading! Yes, I'd love to go with you.
じゃあまた後で日程調整しましょう。
Alright, let's coordinate our schedules later.
はい。ではそんな鷹嶺ルイさんには、
Yes. Well then, for Takane Lui-san,
大好評のカバー曲「ラブカ？」を披露していただきます。
she will perform her popular cover song, "Rabuka?"
それではスタンバイお願いします。
Alright, please get ready.
はい、よろしくお願いします！
Yes, here I go!
夢、覚えてらっしゃらないんですか？
You really don't remember your dreams?
多分、熟睡してるんじゃないかな。ポルカ。
Maybe I'm just sleeping really soundly. Polka.
あ、それもいいことですね。
Ah, that's a good thing too.
ちなみにポルさん、「ラブカ？」ご存知ですか？
By the way Pol-san, do you know "Rabuka?"?
「ラブカ？」流行ったやつだよね。
"Rabuka?" It's the one that went viral, right?
そうですね、若い人の間で流行ってる。
That's right, it's popular among young people.
ポルさんおいくつ...
Pol-san, how old are you...
あー、まあWikipediaとかで見て。
Ah, well, check Wikipedia.
Wikipediaに載ってらっしゃるんですね。
So you're on Wikipedia.
載ってる載ってる、多分。
It's on there, probably.
※載っていません
*It is not listed
長いからね、これも。
It's been a long time, after all.
あ、そうですね。今回で何回目でしたっけ？
Ah, that's right. Which time was it this time?
後でマネージャーさんに確認してください。
Please check with the manager later.
61回目でもマネージャーには頼りたい？
Even for the 61st time, you want to rely on your manager?
準備ができましたのでいきましょう。
We're ready, so let's start.
それでは参りましょう。鷹嶺ルイで「ラブカ？」
Let's begin. Takane Lui with "Rabuka?"
ラブカ？ / 作詞・作曲：柊キライ
Rabuka? / Lyrics/Music: Hiiragi Kirai
暗い 暗い 深海 ヴェールに包まれるは ララララ ラブか？
Dark, dark, deep sea, wrapped in a veil, is it la-la-la-la love?
奪い 奪い 叶わぬ願いは打ち上げられ ささささっと去るか？
Stealing, stealing, unattainable wishes are washed ashore, will you leave in a flurry?
届け 届け それでも光は潰え水面 その遥か ラブか
Reach, reach, even so, the light fades on the surface, far beyond that, is it love?
クライ クライ 未開の想いは足らぬ 足らぬ 至らぬはラブか？
Crying, crying, unexplored feelings are not enough, not enough, is falling short what love is?
ラブか ラララ ラブか
Is it love? La-la-la love
ラブなのか？
Is it love?
甘きラビュー ラビュー ラビューか それはバグ バグ バグか？
Sweet love, love, love? Or is it a bug, bug, bug?
嘘と嘘で濁ったアイ アイ アイニージューか？
Is it I, I, I need you, muddied with lies and lies?
腐る愛 愛 愛か 咀嚼 吐き出し泣くか？
Is it rotting love, love, love? Chewing it up, spitting it out and crying?
届かぬ距離で待っていたってしようがない
It's no use waiting at an unreachable distance
白亜病 ララララ ラブか
Chalky disease, la-la-la-la is it love?
暗い 暗い 深海 ヴェールに包まれるは ララララ ラブか？
Dark, dark, deep sea, wrapped in a veil, is it la-la-la-la love?
奪い 奪い 叶わぬ願いは打ち上げられ ささささっと去るか？
Stealing, stealing, unattainable wishes are washed ashore, will you leave in a flurry?
届け 届け それでも光は潰え水面 その遥か ラブか
Reach, reach, even so, the light fades on the surface, far beyond that, is it love?
クライ クライ 未開の想いは足らぬ 足らぬ 至らぬはラブか？
Crying, crying, unexplored feelings are not enough, not enough, is falling short what love is?
クライ クライ 未開の想いは
Cry, cry... My unexplored feelings are...
足らぬ 足らぬ 至らぬは ラブか?
...not enough, not enough. Is what's missing love?
ラブカ ラララ ラブカ
Love-ka, la la la Love-ka
ラブなのか?
Is it love?
甘きラビュー ラビュー ラビュー ラビューか?
Sweet love-view, love-view, love-view, love-view?
それはバグ バグ バグか?
Is that a bug, bug, bug?
嘘と嘘で濁った
Muddied by lies and lies...
アイ アイ アイニージュか?
...is it "I, I, I need you"?
腐る愛 愛 愛か?
Is it rotting love, love, love?
咀嚼 吐き出し泣くか?
Chewing, spitting out, will I cry?
届かぬ距離で待っていたって
There's no point in waiting...
しょうがない
...at an unreachable distance.
甘きラビュー ラビュー ラビュー ラビューか?
Sweet love-view, love-view, love-view, love-view?
それはバグ バグ バグか?
Is that a bug, bug, bug?
腐るラビュー ラビュー ラビューは
Rotting love-view, love-view, love-view...
既に地に落ち絶えた
...has already fallen to the ground and died out.
届く距離で出会って
If meeting at a reachable distance...
嫌になるならやめな
...makes you hate it, then just stop.
白亜病 ラララ ラララ ラブカ
Hakua-byo, la la la la la la Love-ka
ラララ ラララ ラブカ
La la la la la la Love-ka
はい、続いてはいぬたかししらむです！
Okay, next up is Inu-Taka-Shishi-Ramu!
いぬたかししらむ
Inu-Taka-Shishi-Ramu
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you!
これ、みんな、どういうグループなの？
So, what kind of group is this everyone?
あ、えっとですね、あのー、アニマル・フレンズ的な。
Ah, well, it's like an "Animal Friends" thing.
みんなでね、耳も付いたり、動物だったりするんですよ。
Everyone has ears, we're all animals.
ししろんはちょっとマイク足りなかったのかな？
Was Botan-chan a bit short on microphones?
ちょっとマイク、ね、足りなかったらしくて。自分の中になかったんっす。なんで、ちょっところさんにマイク借りて...
It seems like we didn't have enough mics. I didn't have one. So I'm borrowing Korone-san's...
目の前出てます、本当に。
It's right in front of you, really.
こ、ころねさんは喋れる？大丈夫？
C-Can Korone-san talk? Is it okay?
あ、大丈夫ですね。
Ah, it's okay.
逆に二人で、ちょっとマイク分け合って...
On the contrary, the two of you sharing the mic...
よろしくお願いします。
Please take care of it.
間で、間で、わためぇ。ごめんね。
Between us, between us, Watame. Sorry.
あいだで... ラムちゃんがね。
Between... Lamb-chan is...
すごいね。
That's amazing.
そうですね。なんかこう引きの画面で見てると、皆さん動物だらけなので、なんかいいですね。
Yeah. Looking at it from this wide shot, you're all animals, so it's quite nice.
いぬたかししらむ、コンコン、ネックネックで。はい。
Inu-Taka-Shishi-Ramu, kon-kon, neck-neck. Yes.
あの、ラムの方がいらっしゃるんですね。
So, there's a "lamb" among you.
食材？
Ingredients?
一人だけ食材...？ いぬたかししらむ 角巻わため
Only one person is food...? Inu-Taka-Shishi-Ramu Watame Tsunomaki
一人だけ食材...？ラムはなんでラムなの？
Only one person is food...? Why is the lamb here?
そっちに聞いてるんだよ！ゲストの方に一人一人聞いてるんだよ！
I'm asking you guys! I'm asking the guests one by one!
でもなんか、よく見たら周りの「いぬ、たか、しし」...
But, looking closely, the surroundings are "Dog, Hawk, Lion"...
羊、食べますか？
Do you eat sheep?
まあ、美味しいよね。美味しいよ。
Well, it's delicious. It is.
ラムしゃぶかな？
Maybe lamb shabu-shabu?
ということですね！
There you have it!
弱肉強食！はい、今夜はそんな、えー、ちょっと美味しそうな皆さんがね、
Survival of the fittest! Yes, tonight, these "delicious-looking" guests will...
魅力を存分に伝える楽曲を披露して頂けるんですよね。
...perform a song that fully conveys their charm.
はい、美味しそうな皆さんがちょっと気になったんですけども、
Yes, I was a bit concerned about the "delicious-looking" part, but...
画面の前の皆さんも一緒に盛り上がって頂ければなと思います。
...I hope everyone watching also gets excited with us.
はい、それではスタンバイ、お願いします！
Alright then, please get ready!
はーい、お願いしまーす！
Okay!
意外と我々雑食ですから、意外と皆さんイケるのではないのでしょうかね。
We're actually omnivores, so maybe we can all go for it.
一番あのなかで、やっぱりカースト的な、食べられる的なのだと、羊？
In terms of hierarchy, the most likely to be eaten would be the sheep?
ま、そうですね、やはりラムが美味しいかと思うんですけども。
Well, yeah, I think lamb is delicious.
ラムしゃぶ。ラムしゃぶ美味しいですね。
Lamb shabu-shabu. It's delicious.
ああ、美味しいだろうね、さぞかし。
Ah, it must be, truly.
いいですね。この後じゃあちょっと、食べに行きますか？
Nice. Shall we go eat some after this?
あ、いいですね、行きましょう！
Ah, sounds good, let's go!
それでは参りましょう、いぬたかししらむで、「weeek」！どうぞ！
Now, let's get started. Inu-Taka-Shishi-Ramu with "weeek"! Here you go!
明日からまた 日 月 火 ほら 水 木 回って 金 土 日曜
From tomorrow it's Sun, Mon, Tue again. Look, Wed, Thu, then Fri, Sat, Sunday.
夢の日々を 大事にいきましょう
Let's live our dream days with care.
もういっちょ!
Once more!
明日からまた 日 月 火 ほら 水 木 回って 金 土 日曜
From tomorrow it's Sun, Mon, Tue again. Look, Wed, Thu, then Fri, Sat, Sunday.
僕ら日々を 楽しんで生きてこう
Let's enjoy our days as we live.
さあ行くぞ!
Here we go!
月曜始まった いつもの日々
Monday's started, the usual days.
思い焦がれた週末遠い
The weekend I long for is far away.
火曜水曜 なれてきたご様子
Tuesday, Wednesday, I'm getting used to it.
作った笑顔 引きつったかも!?
Was my fake smile a bit forced!?
気が付きゃ木曜 相当重要
Before I knew it, it's Thursday. Very important.
明日の夜からの予定は未定だから
Since my plans from tomorrow night are undecided...
金曜一日考えよう
Let's think about it all Friday.
自由で壁を ぶち壊し行こう
Let's break down the walls with freedom.
日々生き抜いて 心は曇り
Surviving the days, my heart is cloudy.
僕たちは 過ぎ去っていく
We are passing by.
歩む心を 諦めたら
If you give up on your walking heart...
そこで負けだ お気楽に行こう
...that's where you lose. Let's go easy.
明日からまた 日 月 火 ほら 水 木 回って 金 土 日曜
From tomorrow it's Sun, Mon, Tue again. Look, Wed, Thu, then Fri, Sat, Sunday.
夢の日々を 大事にいきましょう
Let's live our dream days with care.
もういっちょ!
Once more!
明日からまた 日 月 火 ほら 水 木 回って 金 土 日曜
From tomorrow it's Sun, Mon, Tue again. Look, Wed, Thu, then Fri, Sat, Sunday.
僕ら日々を 楽しんで生きてこう
Let's enjoy our days as we live.
さあ行くぞ!
Here we go!
もうどうしようもない模様
It seems there's nothing more I can do.
やる事いっぱいで気持ちは完敗
So much to do, my spirit is completely defeated.
一日4時間睡眠で
Sleeping 4 hours a day...
日々この体力を注ぎ込んで
...pouring my energy into every day.
大人になるってどういう事？
What does it mean to become an adult?
外面良くして35歳を過ぎた頃 オレ達どんな顔？
When we're past 35 and keeping up appearances, what kind of faces do we have?
かっこいい大人になれてるの？
Have we become cool adults?
日々を生き抜いて心は曇り
Surviving each day, our hearts are clouded
僕たちは過ぎ去っていく
We are passing by
ゆっくりでいい やめないで
Slowly is fine, don't stop
いつか水滴 必ず石を穿つ
Someday, water droplets will surely pierce the stone
明日からまた 日、月、火、水、木、金、土、日曜
From tomorrow again: Sun, Mon, Tue, Wed, Thu, Fri, Sat, Sun
夢の日々を 大事にいきましょう
Let's cherish our dream days
もういっちょ！
One more time!
明日からまた 日、月、火、水、木、金、土、日曜
From tomorrow again: Sun, Mon, Tue, Wed, Thu, Fri, Sat, Sun
僕ら日々を楽しんで生きていこう
Let's live enjoying our days
さあ行くぞ！
Here we go!
繰り返しの毎日で行き場のない この気持ち
In the repetitive days with nowhere to go, this feeling
めぐりめくる めまぐるしく回る
Turning over and over, spinning dizzyingly
毎日を泳ぐんだ
Swimming through every day
めげずにLaugh Laugh もういっちょ！
Without giving in, Laugh Laugh, one more time!
明日からまた 日、月、火、水、木、金、土、日曜
From tomorrow again: Sun, Mon, Tue, Wed, Thu, Fri, Sat, Sun
夢の日々を 大事にいきましょう
Let's cherish our dream days
もういっちょ！
One more time!
明日からまた 日、月、火、水、木、金、土、日曜
From tomorrow again: Sun, Mon, Tue, Wed, Thu, Fri, Sat, Sun
僕ら日々を楽しんで生きていこう
Let's live enjoying our days
明日からまた 日、月、火、水、木、金、土、日曜
From tomorrow again: Sun, Mon, Tue, Wed, Thu, Fri, Sat, Sun
夢の日々を 大事にいきましょう
Let's cherish our dream days
もういっちょ！
One more time!
明日からまた 日、月、火、水、木、金、土、日曜
From tomorrow again: Sun, Mon, Tue, Wed, Thu, Fri, Sat, Sun
僕ら日々を楽しんで生きていこう
Let's live enjoying our days
400万再生Over 太鼓の達人 収録 / 鷹嶺ルイ1st original song 柊キライ書き下ろし
Over 4 million views. Recorded in Taiko no Tatsujin. Takane Lui's 1st original song written by Hiiragi Kirai.
世界征服やーやーやー 果たすその日まで
World conquest yah yah yah, until the day it's fulfilled
メンメン毒やーやーやー あなたの周りもヨーヨーヨー
Men-men poison yah yah yah, around you too yo-yo-yo
世界征服アレアレア 約束の地まで
World conquest ale ale ah, to the promised land
さあ掲げよバッテンバッテン メンメン毒やーやーやー
Now raise the cross, cross; men-men poison yah yah yah
大空へ
To the great sky
向かい風受けて 高く高く飛び立とう
Receiving the headwind, let's fly higher and higher
また雨が降り出しても 私が守るから
Even if it starts raining again, I'll protect you
鷹嶺ルイ2nd original song 杉山勝彦書き下ろし
Takane Lui's 2nd original song written by Katsuhiko Sugiyama.
だけど
However...
だけど信じている 君とならどこまでも行ける
But I believe that with you, I can go anywhere
続いてはSSSの3人です。
Next up is the three members of SSS.
ろしくお願いしまーす！
Pleased to be here!
元気！元気ですね。
Energetic! You're energetic.
初登場。
First appearance.
そうですね。
That's right.
緊張してます。
We're nervous.
これ気になったんだけど、SSSの意味はどういうことかな？
I was curious about this, what does SSS mean?
えっ、頭文字から来てまして、セクシー、センシティブ、戦士です。
Well, it comes from the first letters: Sexy, Sensitive, and Warrior.
戦士は... 戦士は漢字なんだね。
Warrior... Warrior is in Kanji.
そうそう。読めない、でも戦士は漢字で。
Right, right. Can't read it, but Warrior is in Kanji.
セクシー入っているということは、何かセクシーなエピソードがあるんでしょうか？
Since 'Sexy' is in it, does that mean there's some sexy episode?
いや、そうなんですよ。ちょっとね、えっちしょこらでこの3人でコラボした時に
Well, yes. When the three of us collaborated on 'Ecchi Choco',
チョコの家で、まあこの3人じゃれ合いまして、もうここでは言えないようなことしまして
at Choco's house, well, the three of us were fooling around and did things I can't say here.
ちょっと、すいません。なんか興奮してまして。
Wait, sorry. I'm getting excited.
あ、興奮してまして本当に申し訳ございません。
Ah, she's excited. We're very sorry.
ここではちょっと言えない内容になってまして。
It's content we can't really talk about here.
言えない内容。
Content you can't say.
えっ、えっちしょこら？
Wait, 'Ecchi Choco'?
えっ、えっちしょこらじゃない、えっちしょこら。
Wait, not 'Ecchi Choco', 'Ecchi Choco'.
なるほどね。
I see.
そうなるるとその、マリンさんは？
In that case, Marine-san?
マリンさんもえっちしょこら。
Marine-san was also 'Ecchi Choco'?
あ、ちょっと、あの日はえっちしょこらやらせていただきましたけど。
Ah, well, that day I did participate in 'Ecchi Choco',
言えないようなことをやってたので、詳しくちょっとあまりこの番組ではね。
but we were doing things I can't really say, so I won't go into detail on this program.
言えないことここに持って来たね。
You brought things you can't say here, didn't you?
そうですね。まあそんな3人なんですけどもね。
That's right. Well, that's the kind of trio we are.
え、もしかして、一緒にやりたいですか？
Eh, by any chance, do you want to join us?
いや、私は大丈夫ですね。
No, I'm fine.
ポルさんはどうです？
How about you, Pol-san?
気になる。気になる。
I'm curious. I'm curious.
でも曲をね、聴いていただいてから ちょっとポルさんも決めていただくということで。
But we'll have Pol-san decide after listening to the song.
今夜はセクシーな楽曲を披露していただけるんですよね。
Tonight you'll be performing a sexy song, right?
そうなんですよ。もう本当にセクシーな私たちにぴったりの楽曲なので、
That's right. It's a song that's perfect for the very sexy us,
見ている君たちをメロメロにしちゃいたいと思います！
so we want to make all of you watching fall head over heels!
メロメロに...
Turning you head over heels...
メロメロも自分で言うこと...
Saying "head over heels" yourself...
セクシーも自分で言うのもすごい。いやぁ、戦士か？これが。
And saying "sexy" yourself is also amazing. Wow, is she a warrior? This...
令和の戦士ね。
The Reiwa warrior, right.
スタンバイしていただきましょうかね。ではお願いします。
Let's have them get ready. Well then, please start.
はい、お願いします！
Yes, please do!
令和の戦士な...
The Reiwa warrior, huh...
令和の戦士、いいですね。でも令和も...戦士で悪くないかもね。
Reiwa warrior is good. But a Reiwa... warrior might not be bad either.
そうですね。セクシーね。
That's right. Sexy, right.
セクシー...ちょっと感じでいきましょうか。戦士。
Sexy... let's go with that vibe. Warrior.
戦士。
Warrior.
それでは参りましょう。威風堂々。
Well then, let's begin. Ifuudoudou.
威風堂々
Ifuudoudou
時には噛んだりして 痛みを覚えさせて
Sometimes biting, making me remember the pain...
溢れる液体で汚してよ全部
Soil everything with overflowing liquid.
足の先からずっと這わせたその神経はもう
The nerves that have been crawling from the tips of the toes already...
感触に溺れる身体心をつれて
Taking the body and heart drowning in the sensation.
指くわえた我慢の中欲してんのが理想？
Is it ideal to want what you're holding back while biting your finger?
いらない全てはいらない 磨き上げてる邪魔なPRIDE
I don't need it, I don't need anything, this annoying, polished PRIDE.
無意味な世界のルールくらい無駄としか言い様がない
The rules of this meaningless world are nothing but a waste.
隠しているあなたのSTYLE 剥き出しにあるがままDIVE
Your hidden STYLE, DIVE as you are, exposed.
そこに生まれるのは期待外れなんかじゃない頂のSMILE
What's born there is not a disappointment, it's the ultimate SMILE.
吐息を合わせた相性 耳に吹きかける感情
Chemistry with synchronized sighs, emotions whispered in the ear.
破裂しそうな胸 騒ぎ出す細胞
A chest about to explode, cells starting to stir.
脱ぎかけてるシャツ 優しくあしらいてよまず構わず
A shirt being taken off, treat me gently first, don't mind.
get flyingも有り 躊躇わないで darlin'
Getting flying is also an option, don't hesitate, darlin'.
自由な世界のど真ん中 夢見てんのが本性?
Is it your true nature to be dreaming in the middle of a free world?
いらない全てはいらない 怯気づいた野望のTRY
I don't need it, I don't need anything, the TRY of a fearful ambition.
満足なんてそこにない 目に見える哀れな未来
There is no satisfaction there, only a visible, pitiful future.
思い通りにできるLIFE 手にできるかはあなた次第
A LIFE you can have your way, whether you can get it is up to you.
隠したりなんかはしない 誰よりも誇らしげにできるMIND
I won't hide anything, a MIND that can be prouder than anyone else.
ホラこの世界の中 他にはない確かなもの 自分以外は皆無
Look, in this world, there is nothing else certain besides myself.
小さくなってる場合じゃない いつだってNo Time ALL RIGHT
This is no time to be making yourself small, it's always No Time ALL RIGHT.
上限値超えエンジン全開でいっちゃえ BURN BURN BURN
Exceed the upper limit, go full throttle with the ENGINE, BURN BURN BURN.
欲しがってんのはそう 気持ちいいの more...
What you're wanting is, yes, more of what feels good...
あるがままの想いでDANCE イイナリでGET DOWN!
DANCE with your thoughts as they are, GET DOWN as you're told!
いらない全てはいらない 磨き上げてる邪魔なPRIDE
I don't need it, I don't need anything, this annoying, polished PRIDE.
無意味な世界のルールくらい無駄としか言い様がない
The rules of this meaningless world are nothing but a waste.
隠しているあなたのSTYLE 剥き出しにあるがままDIVE
Your hidden STYLE, DIVE as you are, exposed.
そこに生まれるのは期待外れなんかじゃない頂のSMILE
What's born there is not a disappointment, it's the ultimate SMILE.
ホラこの世界で今 解き放って
Look, release it now in this world...
鋭くギラつかせた希望 もっと本気出していいよ
The sharply glittering hope, you can be more serious.
はい、続いてはおにかんの二人です。
Next up is the duo, Onikan.
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you! / Please look forward to us!
おにかん
Onikan
おにかん。この二人ほんと仲いいよね。今日も何か仲良しエピソードある？
Onikan. These two are really close, aren't they. Is there any "close relationship" episode today?
仲いい...え、え、え...
Close... eh, eh, eh...
最近の仲良しエピソード
Recent Close Relationship Episode
実はですね、先ほどあの...シュークリームを一つ分けてましたね。
Actually, earlier... they were sharing one cream puff.
あ、そうなんですよ。いただきました、二人で。
Ah, that's right. We had it, the two of us.
え、どうやって分けたの？皮とクリーム？
Eh, how did you share it? The shell and the cream?
一つ余ってるのを、ルイさんがあやめさんに「いる？」みたいなのを。
Lui-san asked Ayame-san "Do you want it?" about the one that was left over.
中身ギュウポウからさ、あれどうやって...?
Since the inside is packed, how did you...?
そういうわけじゃなくて、一つまるまる貰った...
It's not like that, she got the whole thing...
まるまる貰った？食べたいって言ってたんだよね。
She got the whole thing? She was saying she wanted to eat it, right.
いいの？それルイ君は。
Is that okay? For Lui-kun.
まあ何か...まあ甘やかしてもいいかなみたいな。
Well... I thought maybe I could spoil her.
えー、大人だねー。
Wow, so mature.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you.
そういうのがいい関係性を保ってるコツみたいな感じなの？毎週のように会ってますね。
Is that like the secret to maintaining a good relationship? You meet almost every week, right.
だいたい週一で会ってますね。
We meet about once a week.
もうすごい。え、そんな会う？
Wow. Eh, do you meet that much?
私はちょっとあまり...
I don't really...
ないんですけども、やっぱり仲が良いということでね。
Not really, but they are close, aren't they?
仲が良い証拠ってことだね。
That's proof of their good relationship.
はい。じゃあもう今日もすごい協調性...
Yes. So, today too, great cooperation...
調教性？協調性！
Taming-ness? Cooperation!
あ、合ってましたよ、最初に。
Ah, it was correct at first.
楽しみだね。
I'm looking forward to it.
そうですね、ではお二人にスタンバイしていただきましょう。
Indeed. Well then, let's have the two of them standby.
よろしくお願いします！
Please!
よろしくお願いしますー！
Nice to meet you!
ちょっと調教性だとちょっと女幹部が強すぎるかと思いまして。
I thought 'taming-ness' made the 'female executive' vibe too strong.
まあ、鬼と幹部で鬼官だからね。
Well, it's 'Oni' and 'Executive', so 'Oni-Kan'.
そうですね。協調性で合ってる？
Right. Is 'cooperation' correct?
協調性で大丈夫。協調性ね。
Cooperation is fine. Cooperation.
はい。調教だとまたちょっと上下関係がすごいことになっちゃいますので。
Yes. Because if it's 'taming', the hierarchy would get intense.
ああ、でも鬼と幹部ってさ、実際どっちが上なんだろうね？
Ah, but between an Oni and an Executive, which one is actually higher?
どうなんですかね？力目的にはやはり鬼のほうが...
I wonder? In terms of power, the Oni is probably...
なんですけども、やはりあやめさん少しあのおさないところがありますので。
However, Ayame-san has a bit of a childish side.
シュークリームでご機嫌だから。
She's happy with cream puffs.
はい、ではそれでは参りましょう。
Alright, then let's get to it.
このお二人でね、この曲を聴きたかった人も多いのではないでしょうか。
I'm sure many people wanted to hear this song from these two.
おにかんで、チューリングラブ。
By Oni-Kan, Turing Love.
あー、恋の定義がわかんない
Ah, I don't understand the definition of love
まずスキって基準もわかんない
I don't even know the criteria for 'liking' someone
要は、恋してるときが恋らしい
In short, it seems like being in love is annoying
客観？主観？エビデンスプリーズ！
Objective? Subjective? Evidence please!
愛は計算じゃ解けない
Love can't be solved by calculation
まず普通の計算も解けない
I can't even solve a normal calculation first
要は、そんな状態が愛らしい
In short, that state is adorable
アイノウ？ユーノウ？
I know? You know?
もう大抵の事象においてQがあってAを導き出して解けるのに
In the majority of phenomena, there's a Q and an A, and it can be solved
勘違って間違って解のないこの気持ちはなんなんだろう
Mistaking, erring, what is this feeling that has no answer?
（検証は不明瞭）
(Verification is unknown)
DAZING!! モーションは相対性にステイ
DAZING!! Emotion is relativity mystery
チューリングラブ 見つめあったったって解けないメロウ
Turing Love, even if we gaze at each other, it's an unsolvable mellow
ワットイズラブ いま123で明かそうか
What is love, let's reveal it with 1 2 3 now
言葉で生み出すクエスチョン（クエスチョン！）
Question created by words (Question!)
ハートで高鳴るアンサー（アンサー！）
Answer echoing in the heart (Answer!)
測ったって不確定生 ぼくらのBPM
Even if it's measured, it's uncertain, our BPM
チューリングラブ 宙に舞ったったって信じないけど
Turing Love, even if it dances in the air, I won't believe it, but...
フォールインラブ いまはABC すら分かりそうだ
Fall in love, now it seems like I'll understand up to ABC
なんでか教えてオイラー（オイラー！）
Tell me why, Euler (Euler!)
感想きかせてフェルマー（フェルマー！）
Let me hear your thoughts, Fermat (Fermat!)
予測不可能生 いま触れてみる
Unpredictable, I'm touching it now
さあ証明しよう（証明しよう）間違いのないように
Now, let's prove it (Let's prove it), so there are no mistakes
証明しよう（証明しよう）この感情全部全部
Let's prove it (Let's prove it), all of this feeling
証明しよう（証明しよう）正解があるなら
Let's prove it (Let's prove it), if there's a correct answer
証明しよう（証明しよう）シンプルなQ.E.D.
Let's prove it (Let's prove it), a simple Q.E.D.
今日こそ証明したい！（しよう！）
I want to prove it today! (Let's do it!)
目に視えない 無理難題を
Invisible, impossible tasks
ASAP! 導き出したい たどり着きたい 最適解へ
ASAP! I want to lead out, I want to reach the optimal solution
何度空回ったって ぶつかっちゃったって
No matter how many times I go in circles or crash
不可思議なこのアノマリーを解き明かす過程さえ必要条件です
Solving this mysterious anomaly is a prerequisite
「3次元(立体)における2点A,B間の距離を求めよ。」
Find the distance between two points A and B in a 3D space (solid)
的な感じだと思ってたのに
I thought it was that kind of feeling...
座標も公式も見当たらないし 参考資料にも載っていないから
I can't find the coordinates or the formula, and it's not in the reference materials
君と生み出してみせたいじゃん
I want to show you that I can create it with you
3次元(世界)におけるこの気持ちの求め方
How to find this feeling in the 3D world
〇だって×だって 不安にとってイコールで
Circle, cross, they're equal to anxiety
近くなって遠くなって 揺れるこの気持ちの針も
Getting closer, getting further, the needle of this feeling also...
条件は明瞭
Condition is clear
STEPPIN'!! モーションは相愛性ミステイク
STEPPIN'!! Emotion is phase-matching mistake
チューリングラブ 騒ぎ出した胸の痛くなるほど
Turing Love, the chest that started making noise, enough to hurt
証明はいまも 確度を増しているようだ
The proof seems to be gaining certainty now
曖昧も除外して
Excluding ambiguities too
最大の仮説を
The biggest hypothesis
いま、ふたりなら実証できそう
Now, if it's the two of us, we can demonstrate it
チューリングラブ 見つめあったったって解けないメロウ
Turing Love, even if we gaze at each other, it's an unsolvable mellow
ワットイズラブ いま123で明かそうか
What is love, let's reveal it with 1 2 3 now
言葉で生み出すクエスチョン（クエスチョン！）
Question created by words (Question!)
ハートで高鳴るアンサー（アンサー！）
Answer echoing in the heart (Answer!)
測ったって不確定生 ぼくらのBPM
Even if it's measured, it's uncertain, our BPM
チューリングラブ 宙に舞ったったってその因果も
Turing Love, even if it dances in the air, including its results
フォールインラブ いまはXYZ まで分かりそうだ
Fall in love, now it seems like I'll understand up to XYZ
確かめさせてピタゴラス（ピタゴラス！）
Let me verify, Pythagoras (Pythagoras!)
確かにさせてリーマン（リーマン！）
Make it certain, Riemann (Riemann!)
予測済み可変性 いま触れてみる
Predicted variability, I'm touching it now
さあ証明しよう（証明しよう）間違いのないように
Now, let's prove it (Let's prove it), so there are no mistakes
証明しよう（証明しよう）この感情全部全部
Let's prove it (Let's prove it), all of this feeling
証明しよう（証明しよう）正解があるなら
Let's prove it (Let's prove it), if there's a correct answer
証明しよう（証明しよう）推測を超えて！
Let's prove it (Let's prove it), beyond speculation!
証明しよう（証明しよう）間違いのないように
Let's prove it (Let's prove it), so there are no mistakes
証明しよう（証明しよう）この感情全部全部
Let's prove it (Let's prove it), all of this feeling
証明しよう（証明しよう）正解があるなら
Let's prove it (Let's prove it), if there's a correct answer
証明しよう（証明しよう）シンプルなQ.E.D.
Let's prove it (Let's prove it), a simple Q.E.D.
続いてはルイすいの二人です！
Next up is the duo Luisui!
よろしくお願いしますー！
Nice to meet you!
あの二人がね、何を歌ってくれるのかって、かなり注目されてると思う。
I think people are really interested in what those two are going to sing.
ありがとうございます。ありがとうございます。
Thank you. Thank you.
本日二人で披露してくれる曲は？
What song will you two perform today?
じゃあ、何？聞いちゃっていい？
So, what is it? Can I ask?
はい。今日は『バグ』を歌わせていただきます。
Yes. Today, we'll be singing "Bug."
おおー！
Oh!
あ、バグご存知ですか？バグ。
Ah, do you know "Bug"? "Bug."
あのバ、バグってるやつかな？
Is it the one that's, like, glitching out?
バグってバグって、あのかっこいいやつだね。
Glitching and glitching... that cool one, right?
かっこいいやつです！間違いない。
It's the cool one! Definitely.
僕も知ってるよ。僕も知ってるからね。
I know it too. I know it, you see.
なんで今回は『バグ』を選んだのでしょう？
Why did you choose "Bug" this time?
私自身がちょっと歌を頑張りたいって思った時に...
When I decided I wanted to work harder on my singing...
やはり同じ事務所のすいせい先輩には、歌ですごく憧れておりまして。
I've always looked up to Suisei-senpai from the same agency for her singing.
で、一緒にもし歌えるんだったら、かっこいい曲を一緒に歌えたらなってことで...
And I thought if we could sing together, I'd love to do a cool song...
『バグ』でお誘いさせていただきました。ありがとうございます。
So I invited her to sing "Bug." Thank you.
ちょっと緊張してる？鷹嶺君。
Are you a little nervous, Takane-kun?
緊張してます！
I'm nervous!
なんかさっきまでと大違いというか。本当ですか？あ、出ちゃった。
You're like a completely different person than a moment ago. Really? Oh, it's showing.
でもその先輩後輩の、先輩のすいせいさん、最近後輩との温かいエピソードみたいのもある？
But as the senpai in this dynamic, Suisei-san, do you have any recent heartwarming stories with your kouhai?
二人の温かいエピソード
Heartwarming story between the two
急ですね！温かいエピソードか。
That's sudden! A heartwarming story...
ルイさんとの温かいエピソードは、この『バグ』のコーラスがあるんですけど...
A heartwarming story with Lui-san is about the chorus of "Bug"...
ほぼ取ってくれました。
She recorded almost all of it for me.
さすが後輩！
That's our kouhai!
二人の温かいエピソード...？
Heartwarming story...?
私が録れずじまいでいたところを、「私が録ります！」ということで。
When I was stuck and couldn't record it, she said, "I'll do it!"
「お任せください、じゃあ録ります」と。ありがとうございます本当に。
She said, "Leave it to me, I'll record it." Thank you so much, really.
じゃあ皆さん今日は、あの、撮りだめ...撮りだけに？
So today, everyone, it's... just the recording?
撮りだけに。何だこれ、まあいいか。
Just the recording. What's with that? Oh well.
じゃあ今日は裏のコーラスも注目だね。注目していきましょう。
Then we should pay attention to the background chorus too. Let's keep an eye out.
それでは、スタンバイの方よろしくお願いします！
All right, please head to your positions!
よろしくお願いします。
Thank you.
撮りだけに。
Just the recording.
撮りだけにだそうですね。出ましたね、今回も。
It seems it's "just the recording." There it is again.
出ましたか？出ましたね。
Did it? It did.
温かいエピソードというか、なんか凍えるエピソードみたいになっちゃいそうでしたけど。
Rather than a heartwarming story, it almost felt like a freezing one.
ちょっと寒かった気がしますけど、最後で良かったね。
It felt a bit chilly, but I'm glad it ended well.
我々は温かいエピソードありますかね？
Do we have any heartwarming stories?
結構この、今の会場と照明あったかいよ。
The venue and these lights are pretty warm right now.
結構そうだね、温かいですね。これ61回目ですからね、浴びるの。
That's true, it's warm. It's our 61st time basking in this, after all.
温かいですね。61回目にもなりました。じゃあ、行きましょうか。
Very warm. 61 times already. All right, shall we?
それでは参りましょう。ルイすいで『バグ』、どうぞ！
Now then, let's begin. LuiSui with "Bug." Here we go!
バグ
作詞・作曲：かいりきベア
Bug
Lyrics & Composition: Kairiki Bear
迷子 迷子 真っ只中さあ
Lost, lost, right in the thick of it
パッパラパら パーラノーイ「ア」
Pa-pa-pa-ra, paranoia
ギコギコ MY HEART 剪定
Grind, grind, pruning my heart
パッパラパら パーラノーイ「ア」
Pa-pa-pa-ra, paranoia
退路 退路 断った 絡まった
Retreat, retreat, cut off and entangled
パッパラパら パーラノーイ「ア」
Pa-pa-pa-ra, paranoia
SAD SAD 突っ伏して 「 」
Sad, sad, face down, " "
ぱっぱらパら パーラノイド
Pa-pa-pa-ra, paranoid
さあ バババグさ バグバグ
Now, bu-bu-bug, bug, bug
タタタグ 才能のタグ
Ta-ta-tag, tag of talent
もう ハハハグ 感情は剥ぐ
Now, ha-ha-hug, strip away the emotions
発症「クルシイ」は 嫌嫌嫌 嫌嫌嫌
Outbreak: "It hurts" is no, no, no, no, no, no
まあ！絶叫な感情落下 パッパラノーイ「ア」
Wow! A screaming emotional fall, pa-pa-pa-ra, paranoia
溺れ声上げては ぐるぐる
Raising a drowning voice, round and round
まあ！絶体絶命落下 やったれメッタラ
Wow! A desperate fall, give it your all
沈めユメユメ 嫌嫌嫌
Sinking dreams, no, no, no
さあ バババグさ バグバグ
Now, bu-bu-bug, bug, bug
的ハズレズレ 慈愛嫌嫌
Missing the mark, affection is no, no
さあ バババグさ バグバグ
Now, bu-bu-bug, bug, bug
回答絶え絶え 嫌嫌嫌 嫌嫌嫌
Answers fading away, no, no, no, no, no, no
狂狂 ぱっかーん 警報 待って無理 ぐるぐる
Madness, crack open, alarm, wait, no way, round and round
せーので回れ (狂狂狂)
Turn on three! (Madness, madness, madness)
7777 ぱっかーん 警報 やっぱ無理 ぐるぐる
7777, crack open, alarm, as expected no way, round and round
あんよに鎖 (狂狂狂)
Chains on the feet (Madness, madness, madness)
エンドレス病み...？
Endless sickness...?
抱っこ 抱っこ いらない子だ
Hold me, hold me, I'm an unwanted child
パッパラパら パーラノーイ「ア」
Pa-pa-pa-ra, paranoia
いい子 いい子 「頑張れ」の氾濫
Good child, good child, a flood of "do your best"
アドミニストレイター 嗚咽
Administrator, sobbing
バババグさ バグバグ
Bu-bu-bug, bug, bug
ラララグ ランタイム ラグ
La-la-lag, runtime lag
ロロログ 反抗のログ
Lo-lo-log, log of rebellion
バババグ ぱぱぱらぱぱ パーラノーイ「ア」
Bu-bu-bug, pa-pa-pa-ra-pa-pa, paranoia
パーラノーイ「ア」 嫌嫌
Paranoia, no, no
さあ 絶叫な感情落下 パッパラノーイ「ア」
Now, a screaming emotional fall, pa-pa-pa-ra, paranoia
左右 行方も ぐるぐる 悲惨
Left, right, whereabouts are round and round, tragic
限界 脳狂っちゃって やったれメッタラ
Limit, brain's gone crazy, give it your all
ヤミ迷え酔え イナイイナイばあ イナイイナイ×点
Darkness, get lost, get drunk, Peek-a-boo, Not here, not here x point
絶叫な感情落下 パッパラノーイ「ア」
A screaming emotional fall, pa-pa-pa-ra, paranoia
溺れ声上げては ぐるぐる
Raising a drowning voice, round and round
まあ！絶体絶命落下 やったれメッタラ
Wow! A desperate fall, give it your all
凍え枯れ果て 嫌嫌嫌
Frozen and withered, no, no, no
さあ バババグさ バグバグ
Now, bu-bu-bug, bug, bug
爛れ荒れ荒れ 悲哀 嫌嫌
Festering and roughed up, sorrow, no, no
さあ バババグさ バグバグ
Now, bu-bu-bug, bug, bug
暗闇マミレ理性 嫌嫌嫌 今今今
Reason covered in darkness, no, no, no, now, now, now
嫌嫌嫌 嫌嫌嫌 嫌嫌嫌 嫌嫌嫌 嫌嫌嫌 嫌嫌嫌
No no no, no no no, no no no, no no no, no no no, no no no
皆さんお待たせね。
Everyone, thanks for waiting.
鷹嶺ルイ誕生日記念2023グッズの紹介もしていくよ。
I'm going to introduce the Takane Lui Birthday 2023 goods!
この後22時から発売だから、ぜひぜひチェックしてくださいね。
They'll be on sale from 10 PM tonight, so please check them out.
今回のグッズは4種類用意させていただきました。
We've prepared four types of goods this time.
キャンバスアート、ランダムマグネット、コースター、アイスキューブの4種類となっております。
Canvas art, random magnets, coasters, and ice cubes.
今回ももちろんフルセット購入特典がございます。
Of course, there's a full set purchase bonus again.
数量限定版には、一緒にオムライスを食べる特典ボイス、
The limited edition includes a bonus voice track of us eating omurice together...
そしてそして、私の箔押しメッセージと直筆サイン入りのポストカードが付いております。
...and a postcard with my foil-stamped message and handwritten autograph.
数量限定ですが、たくさん用意したのでルイ友のみんな、
It's a limited quantity, but we've prepared plenty, so I'd be happy if Luitomo...
そしてそうじゃない人もお手元に迎え入れてくれると嬉しいです。
...and others alike could get their hands on them.
通常版は直筆サインのところが箔押しサインになってるよ。
For the regular version, the handwritten signature is foil-stamped.
ではでは、一つずつグッズを見ていきましょう。
Now, let's look at each item one by one.
まずはキャンバスアート。
First, the canvas art.
ぐちこ先生描き下ろしのオムライスをあーんしているイラスト、
This illustration by Guchiko-sensei of me being fed omurice...
めちゃくちゃこれ可愛くないですか？しかもオシャレでしょ。
...isn't it just so cute? And it's stylish, too.
色合いもお部屋に馴染むんじゃないかしら。
I think the colors will blend well with any room.
ぜひお部屋に飾って一緒にご飯食べようね。
Please display it in your room and let's eat together.
続いてはこちら、ランダムマグネット。
Next up is this: random magnets.
トゥーミ先生描き下ろしの可愛い可愛いイラストのマグネット。
These are magnets with very cute illustrations by Toomy-sensei.
全4種類の中からランダムで一つお届けいたします。
You'll receive one random design out of four.
マグネットといえばやっぱり冷蔵庫に貼りたくなるよね。
Speaking of magnets, you just have to stick them on the fridge, right?
4種類全部可愛いから、よろしければコンプリートしてみてくださいね。
All four are cute, so try to complete the set if you can.
ちなみに私はよだれダラーっとしてるのが特にお気に入り。
By the way, my personal favorite is the one where I'm drooling.
続いては、じゃじゃーん、コースター。
Next is... ta-da! The coaster.
飲み物を入れると水滴がついて気になるよね。
Don't you hate it when condensation gets everywhere?
そんな時にこのコースターがおすすめ。
That's when I recommend this coaster.
金属とコルクの素材なので重厚感もあって、
It's made of metal and cork, so it has a nice weight to it...
普段使いでも飾って楽しめるコースターになっているよ。
...and you can use it every day or just display it.
やっぱ冷えた飲み物のグラスをここに置いてプハーとしたいよね。
You'll definitely want to put a cold glass on here and go 'Phew!'
ということで、冷えた飲み物には氷が必要。
And since cold drinks need ice...
最後はアイスキューブの紹介です。
...finally, let me introduce the ice cubes.
私の様々なモチーフが入ったアイスキューブ。
These ice cubes feature various motifs associated with me.
洗って繰り返し使えるのもアイスキューブの良いところ。
A great thing about ice cubes is that they're washable and reusable.
てかさ、このパネル持ってる人誰なんだろう。
By the way, I wonder who's holding these panels...
というわけで、新日本プロレスの支配者、グレート-O-カーンである。
So, I am the Great-O-Khan, the dominator of New Japan Pro-Wrestling.
おい、この余がせっかく直々にグッズを紹介してやったんだ。
Hey, I went through the trouble of personally introducing the goods.
おい、ルイ友は必ず完全支配コンプリートをめざして買えよ！！
You Luitomo had better buy them all and aim for total domination!
おい、それから鷹嶺！貴様この野郎！
And you, Takane! You brat!
おい、なんだって？プロレスが得意なんだって？
Hey, what's this? You're good at pro-wrestling?
しかも、あぁ？誕生日だ？
And what? It's your birthday?
おい、だったらよ。おい！
Well, then... Hey!
これが余からの誕生日プレゼントじゃ。
This is your birthday present from me.
おい、ルイ姫。
Hey, Princess Lui.
誕生日おめでとう。
Happy birthday.
このあと22時から販売開始！
Sales start at 10 PM tonight!
続いては今週のピックアップアーティストのコーナーです。
Next is the 'Weekly Pickup Artist' corner.
今週は海外から今大注目のグループが中継で出演してくれます。
This week, a group that's currently garnering a lot of attention overseas will join us via a live link.
ほー、海外アーティスト。楽しみだね、これ。
Ooh, overseas artists. I'm looking forward to this.
そう、楽しみですね。中継が繋がってる？
Yes, it's exciting. Is the link ready?
そうなんです。中継、繋がっていますので、早速ですが繋いでみましょう。ホロトリのみなさーん！
That's right. The link is ready, so let's connect right away. Everyone from Holotori!
可愛いね。
They're cute.
可愛いですけども。
They are indeed.
あれ？
Wait...
なんかさっきまでこっちにいた人もいる？
Is someone there who was just over here?
そうですね、いらっしゃいますね。早い、早く行った。
You're right, there is. That was fast. They got there fast.
おーい！
Hey!
おい！もしもし！えっ、なんか...
Hey! Hello? Wait, what...
えっ、さっきまでスタジオにいたいつものルイさんじゃないんですか？
Um, aren't you the usual Lui-san who was just in the studio?
あ、なんか聞こえないな。聞こえづらい、聞こえづらいな。
Ah, I can't really hear you. It's hard to hear, hard to hear.
ん、あ、なんかちょっと電波が悪いみたいですね。
Hmm, ah, it seems like the signal is a bit weak.
そうか、まだそういうこともあるんだ。
Ah, I see. I guess that still happens.
なので、改めてまして、ホロトリのみなさんです！
So, once again, here is Holotori!
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you!
ちょっと触れない方が良さそうですので、ホロトリの紹介に参りましょう。
It seems best not to mention it, so let's move on to introducing Holotori.
ホロトリのみなさんがどんなグループなのか、VTRにまとめましたので、ご覧いただきましょう。どうぞ！
We've put together a video showing what kind of group Holotori is, so please take a look. Here you go!
今週のピックアップアーティスト。
Weekly Pickup Artist.
ホロトリ。
Holotori.
JP、ID、ENの国境を超えた、グローバルアイドルユニット、ホロトリ。
A global idol unit that transcends the borders of JP, ID, and EN: Holotori.
メンバーは...
The members are...
IDから孔雀、パヴォリア・レイネ。
Pavolia Reine from ID, the peacock.
ENから不死鳥、小鳥遊キアラ。
Takanashi Kiara from EN, the phoenix.
梟、七詩ムメイ。
Nanashi Mumei, the owl.
JPから鷹、鷹嶺ルイ。
Takane Lui from JP, the hawk.
あひる！？大空スバル。
Oozora Subaru, the duck!?
5羽の鳥からなる、多国語を話せるグループ、ホロトリ。今注目のグループです。
A multilingual group made up of five birds: Holotori. They are the group to watch right now.
そんな個性豊かな彼女たちに今夜披露してもらうのは、
Tonight, these unique girls will perform...
彼女たちの明るさを表現する「にっこり^^調査隊のテーマ」と「セカイ」。
"Niccori^^ Survey Team Theme" and "Sekai," songs that express their brightness.
この「セカイ」、今音楽シーンで欠かせないDECO*27、
"Sekai" is by DECO*27, who is essential to today's music scene...
堀江晶太というホロライブ楽曲も多く手掛けた有名アーティスト2人の夢のコラボ曲。
and Shota Horie. It's a dream collaboration between these two famous artists who have created many Hololive songs.
素晴らしい楽曲とともに、HOLOTORIが世界へ羽ばたきます。
Along with these wonderful songs, HOLOTORI takes flight to the world.
いや、今注目のHOLOTORIのパフォーマンス楽しみですね。
I'm looking forward to the performance by the much-discussed HOLOTORI.
うーん、これは期待できるんじゃないかな。
Yeah, I think we can really expect something great.
そうですね。
That's right.
ちなみに、あの、誰推しとかってありますか？
By the way, do you have a favorite member?
いや、みんなフレッシュな感じですごい可愛かったけどね。
Well, they all felt so fresh and were really cute.
やっぱり箱推し。
So you're a "Hako-oshi" (group supporter).
は、箱推しっていうんだ、それを。
Oh, so that's what you call it.
そうなんです、そうなんです。箱推しって言うんですよね、今では。
Yes, exactly. It's called "Hako-oshi" nowadays.
と、鳥だから？
Because they're birds?
そういうあの巣箱っていう話ではないですね。
It's not about a nesting box (Subako).
あ、違うんだ。
Ah, I see.
では、ではないんですけど。
Well, it's not that, but...
でも、鳥と箱だともうそうなっちゃう。
But with "birds" and "boxes," you'd think that.
そうなってしまうんですけど、それはちょっと失礼いたしました。
It does sound like that, my apologies.
でも、意味はちょっと違ってまして。
But the meaning is a bit different.
グループ全部好きなことを、最近では「箱推し」と。
Supporting the whole group is called "Hako-oshi" lately.
みんなも覚えてってね。
Everyone, remember that.
箱推ししていこう。
Let's support the whole group.
ぜひぜひ箱推しをお願いいたします。
Please, give them your full support.
それでは準備ができたようなので参りましょう。
It looks like they're ready, so let's begin.
HOLOTORIで「にっこり^^調査隊のテーマ」、
HOLOTORI with "Niccori^^ Survey Team Theme"...
「セカイ」、2曲続けてどうぞ。
and "Sekai." Please enjoy these two songs.
にっこり^^調査隊！
Niccori Survey Team!
おはこんばんちわ
Hello, good evening, and good day.
How are you?
今日も今日とて最高です
Today is also the best day ever.
おお〜ん！だほーい！
Ohhh! Daho-i!
コレクション！
Collection!
サンキュー！
Thank you!
1 2 の 3 はい！
1, 2, 3, go!
証拠！
Evidence!
我々は世界の笑顔を調査する！
We shall investigate the world's smiles!
はい隊長！俺に名案が…
Yes, Captain! I have a great idea...
ってまだ何も言ってないんだが？
Wait, I haven't said anything yet!
もーとーにーかく！あれだほら
A-anyway! You know, that thing...
カナブンは一見にしかず？
Seeing a drone beetle is believing?
あ、百聞は一見にしかずだねぇ
Ah, seeing once is better than hearing a hundred times.
それそれ！違うって！
That's it! No, it's not!
隊長！いい名案があります
Captain! I have a great idea.
ぜひ聞かせてほしいものだな
I'd certainly like to hear it.
とりあえず出発しよう ノープランで
For now, let's just set off without a plan.
ちょっと待って！
Wait a minute!
出発進行！
Off we go!
ちょっと待ってってば 旅支度くらいさせろ〜！
I said wait! At least let me pack for the trip!
3 2 1 GO!
じゃお持ち物チェックを始めまーす
Then, let's start the baggage check!
まずは基本の！
First, the basics!
ぱ、ぱぱパスポート持った？
D-d-do you have your passport?
き、きき着替え忘れた！
I f-f-forgot my change of clothes!
も、モバイルバッテリー持った？
D-do you have a portable battery?
こ、恋は持った？
D-did you bring love?
もちろん！
Of course!
仲間がいて 私がいる
I have my friends, and I am here.
しかも普通じゃない
And we're not just ordinary.
だれのことかな？
Who are you talking about?
ぼくらには不可能を可能に変える何かがあるさ
We have something that turns the impossible into possible.
にっこりこりこりこりコリアンダー
Niccori-cori-cori-coriander.
あちらもこちらも
Here, there, and everywhere...
千客万来！
...business is booming!
君の笑顔をコレクションさせて
Let me add your smile to my collection.
いぇい いぇい いぇい いぇい いぇい
Yay yay yay yay yay!
大人（おとな）も子供（こども）も関係ねぇぜ
Adults or children, it doesn't matter.
これぞ一流の エンターテイメント！
This is top-tier entertainment!
わたしだって いつか 夢を叶えてやるって
Even I will make my dreams come true one day.
(We can do it!)
このにっこりに触れて
By touching this "Niccori"...
もっと胸膨らみましたとさ
...my heart swelled even more.
Good!
そのションボリをにっこりに変換
Converting those blues into smiles.
うちらに任せろ make your smile Fu〜
Leave it to us, make your smile, Fu~!
アゲのときだって サゲのときだって
In high times and in low times...
かき混ぜちゃって スパイスだって
...mix it all up, even the spice!
完璧だ！なにが？
Perfect! What is?
にっこりこりこりこりお利口ちゃん
Niccori-cori-cori-cori, good girl.
大人（おとな）も子供（こども）も 熱烈歓迎！
Adults and children are all heartily welcome!
もち我々も調査対象だ
Of course, we are also subjects of the investigation.
Run away うぇい うぇい うぇーい うぇーい
Run away, way-way-way-way!
わたしだって いつか 夢を叶えてやるって
Even I will make my dreams come true one day.
(We can do it!)
このにっこりに触れて
By touching this "Niccori"...
もっと胸膨らみましたとさ
...my heart swelled even more.
ずっと探してたんだよ 特別だって言える場所
I've been searching for a place I can call special.
なんで僕を選んだの？ 笑う君が手を引いたんだ
Why did you choose me? You smiled and took my hand.
だって君はすごいから 負けらんないなって思うんだよ
Because you're amazing, I feel like I can't lose.
どんな時も僕の中に 君の声が鳴り響いていた
At all times, your voice was echoing inside me.
怖いんだ 何にもない僕だけどできるかな
I'm scared. I have nothing, can I really do it?
自信のなさとしょうもなさで一生懸命さ
I'm doing my best despite my lack of confidence and worthlessness.
けど君は「それがどうしたの？」って顔をして
But you had a look on your face like, "What about it?"
歌を歌うじゃない それはずるいじゃない？
You're singing, aren't you? That's not fair, is it?
飛び込んでいこう 僕らのセカイへ
Let's dive in, into our world.
正解の想いに出会えるかな
I wonder if we'll find the "correct" feelings.
歌っていたい 踊っていたい
I want to keep singing, I want to keep dancing.
痛いくらい笑えるように
So that we can laugh until it hurts.
名前をない 僕らの世界を
Our world that has no name...
迷っていけるよ 君となら
...I can wander through it if I'm with you.
変わっていこう 願うように
Let's change, just as we wish.
今僕ら 期待の未体験を
Right now, our anticipated unexperienced moment...
君の未来を僕が歌うよ
...I will sing of your future.
描いてもっと Yeah
Keep on drawing more, yeah.
キミの天国を僕が救うよ 描いてもっと Yeah
I'll save your heaven, draw more, yeah
泣いてもいいじゃん それも答えだ どうしたっていいよ
It's okay to cry, that's an answer too. It's fine either way.
想いは全部 零さないように 抱きしめながら
While holding all my feelings tight so they don't spill...
キミと見たいセカイへ
...towards the world I want to see with you.
ホロ鳥のみなさん、ありがとうございました！
Thank you, Holotori!
ありがとうございましたー
Thank you!
これからの活躍に注目していきたいですよね
We'll definitely want to keep an eye on their future activities.
あ、そうだねこれは。ねー
Ah, that's right. Yeah.
そしてなんと、ミュージックガーデンも残すところ２曲になってしまいました
And believe it or not, there are only two songs left in Music Garden.
え？２曲になったの？
Huh? Only two songs left?
１時間ぐらいの気がしたんだけど
I felt like it's been about an hour.
１時間ぐらいの番組ですよ、こちらね
This is about an hour-long program.
あー。あっという間だったね
Ah. It went by in a flash.
はい、もう時間調整完璧でございます
Yes, the timing is absolutely perfect.
なんとですね、この後の２曲は
Well, you see, the next two songs...
先ほどホロ鳥のみなさんが披露してくださった この『セカイ』という楽曲を作りました...
...the song 'Sekai' that Holotori just performed was composed by...
『セカイ』を作ったわけじゃなくて...
Not like they created "The World"...
『セカイ』という楽曲ですね。それを作ったDECO*27さんと...
The song called "Sekai." Composed by DECO*27 and...
もう一曲が堀江晶太さんが書き下ろした新曲、とのことなんです
...the other one is a new song written by Shota Horie.
２曲も？新曲？
Two songs? New songs?
そうなんです、２曲も新曲がここで！
That's right, two new songs right here!
人に委ねたんだねー
Entrusted them to people, huh?
そうなんですよー。ありがとうございます
Exactly. Thank you.
ということでね、どちらも強いメッセージ性のある楽曲に仕上がってるとのことです
And so, both of them are said to be songs with a strong message.
２曲！
Two songs!
今日一のびっくりですね、ポルカさん
That's the biggest surprise of the day, Polka.
はい。それでは参りましょう
Yes. Well then, let's get to it.
DECO*27さん書き下ろし曲、『ばかばっか』
A song written by DECO*27, "Baka Bakka."
堀江晶太さん書き下ろし曲、『First Cry』
A song written by Shota Horie, "First Cry."
２曲続けてどうぞ！
Please listen to the two songs in a row!
どうぞ！
Go ahead!
ばかばっか / 作詞・作曲: DECO*27
Baka Bakka / Lyrics and Composition: DECO*27
もういいじゃん ムキになっちゃって
Enough already, getting all worked up.
カッコつけて カッコよくない
Acting tough, but it's not cool.
そういうのイヤになってんだ
I'm getting sick of that kind of thing.
ほっといてよ 知りたくない
Leave me alone, I don't want to know.
もういいじゃん やけになってんの？
Enough already, are you getting desperate?
嫉妬したり じっとできない
Being jealous, unable to stay still.
聴こえないよう 耳塞いだって
Even if I plug my ears so I can't hear...
言ってくるじゃん しんどいなあ
...you still talk to me, it's exhausting.
僕は誰も覗かないよ
I won't peek into anyone's life.
だから僕のこと そっとしておいて
So please, just leave me alone.
うざいだけのバカに はい はい はい
To the annoying idiots: "Yes, yes, yes."
ウケる「またのお越し待ってるね」だとか
Hilarious. "We'll be waiting for your next visit," and such.
本当は怯えてる 吠えるだけの弱虫だ だ だ
Actually just a coward who barks because they're scared.
痛いくせに耐えて はい はい はい
Enduring it even though it hurts: "Yes, yes, yes."
いつも平気なフリばっかなの
Always just pretending to be fine.
僕は壁を張ったまま笑う
I'll keep laughing behind my walls.
それ以上近づかないで
Don't get any closer than that.
怖いじゃん
It's scary, isn't it?
ばかばっか ばかばっか
Nothing but idiots, nothing but idiots.
ばかばっか やだ ばかばっか
Nothing but idiots, no, nothing but idiots.
もういいじゃん まだ怒ってんの
Enough already, are you still angry?
ほっといてよ ほっとできない
Leave me alone, you can't be at peace.
見ないように 目を逸らしたって
Even if I look away so I don't see...
付いてくるじゃん やっぱり
...you still follow me, after all.
転がったら起きればいいじゃん
If you fall, just get back up.
失ったら探せばいいじゃん
If you lose it, just look for it.
いや いや いや いや いや いや それでよくない？
No, no, no... Isn't that good enough?
間違ったら直せばいいじゃん
If you're wrong, just fix it.
やんなったらやめればいいじゃん
If you're fed up, just quit.
いや いや いや いや いや いや それでよくない？
No, no, no... Isn't that good enough?
僕は誰も覗かないよ
I won't peek into anyone's life.
だから僕のこと そっとしておいて
So please, just leave me alone.
やなこと全部大丈夫だと言えたらいいのにな
I wish I could say everything bad is okay.
思えたらいいのにな
I wish I could believe that.
違うよ デタラメな大正解
No, it's a nonsensical great answer.
いつも僕は損なロールなの
I'm always stuck in a losing role.
また言いたいことを殺す
I'll kill what I want to say again.
だからもう忘れてくれ
So please, just forget me.
うざいだけのバカに はい はい はい
To the annoying idiots: "Yes, yes, yes."
ウケる「またのお越し待ってるね」だとか
Hilarious. "We'll be waiting for your next visit," and such.
本当は怯えてる 吠えるだけの弱虫だ だ だ
Actually just a coward who barks because they're scared.
痛いくせに耐えて はい はい はい
Enduring it even though it hurts: "Yes, yes, yes."
いつも平気なフリばっかなの
Always just pretending to be fine.
僕は壁を張ったまま笑う
I'll keep laughing behind my walls.
それ以上近づかないで
Don't get any closer than that.
どうか
Please.
ほんとばかばっか いい加減ばっか
Seriously, nothing but idiots, nothing but nonsense.
とんだバグばっか だっせーなーって
Nothing but terrible bugs, how pathetic.
そんなことばっか思う僕もやっぱ
I guess me, who only thinks such things...
どうしようもないんだ 罰点超過
...is hopeless too. Demerits exceeding the limit.
痛いのとか耐えてらんない ない
I can't stand the pain, no, no.
死ねるって僕も口ばっかだね
Saying "I could die," I'm just all talk too.
今日も壁を張ったまま笑う
I'll keep laughing behind my walls today too.
それ以上近づかないで
Don't get any closer than that.
怖いじゃん
It's scary, isn't it?
ばかばっか ほら ばかばっか
Nothing but idiots, see, nothing but idiots.
FIRST CRY
作詞・作曲：堀江晶太
Lyrics/Composition: Horie Shota
誰かに言われなくたって
Even if nobody tells me
私のほうがもっと嫌いだ
I hate myself even more
うるさいな
Be quiet
想像が視界を塞いで
My imagination blocks my view
惨めな理由を書き連ねる
Listing all the miserable reasons
教室にずっと居残り
Staying behind in the classroom forever
窓の向こうに黒い影があって
There's a dark shadow beyond the window
何も言わずにこっちを見ていた
It was looking here without a word
私は貴方に救われたくて泣くんじゃない
I'm not crying because I want you to save me
産声は止められないもの
The first cry is something that can't be stopped
何千回ともう一度 死に損なおう
Let's fail to die thousands of times once more
希望と絶望の夜中を纏って
Wrapped in the midnight of hope and despair
醜い光を許したいのは
The one who wants to forgive the ugly light
他ならない私だった
Is none other than me
息をして 目をあけて
Take a breath, open your eyes
これが最後かどうか
Whether this is the last
知る術はないよ 知りたくもないよ
I have no way of knowing, I don't even want to know
優しいな
So kind
昏昏と闇は寄り添って
Darkness nestles in dizzily
解けない答えを塗り潰した
I painted over the unsolvable answer
どうせ面白くもないよと
Saying it's not interesting anyway
窓を挟んで微かに聞こえた
I heard it faintly through the window
それは祈るような啜り泣きだった
It was a sob like a prayer
私は貴方を救える言葉を知らないけど
I don't know the words that can save you, but...
寂しいねって声をかけた
I called out, "It's lonely, isn't it?"
何千回ともう一度 死に損なおう
Let's fail to die thousands of times once more
希望と絶望の夜中を纏って
Wrapped in the midnight of hope and despair
何千回ともう一度 生きる貴方へ
To you who lives, failing to die thousands of times once more
私も続くよ 窓の向こう側で
I'll follow, on the other side of the window
醜い光を愛せたとき
When I could love the ugly light
終わらせなかった産声を
The first cry that I didn't let end
唄にしよう
Let's make it a song
痛いのとか耐えてらんないない 死ねるって僕も口ばっかだね
I can't stand the pain, I'm all talk about being able to die
今日も壁を貼ったまま笑う それ以上近づかないででで 怖いじゃん
Today too, I laugh with a wall up. Don't come any closer, it's scary
6月11日24時 2曲同時リリース
Simultaneous release of 2 songs at 24:00 on June 11
特報
Special News
もういいじゃん ムキになっちゃって カッコつけて カッコよくない
Enough already, getting all serious. Acting cool, but you're not cool
鷹嶺ルイ NEW ORIGINAL SONG 「ばかばっか」 MV このあと22:00〜プレミア公開!!
Takane Lui NEW ORIGINAL SONG "Bakabakka" MV Premiere release at 22:00 after this!!
そういうの嫌になってんだ ほっといてよ 知りたくないよ
I'm sick of that kind of thing. Leave me alone, I don't want to know
楽しくお届けしてきましたMUSIC GARDEN、あっという間にエンディングのお時間になりましたー！
We've been joyfully bringing you MUSIC GARDEN, and in a flash, it's time for the ending!
ポルさん、今日はどうでしたか？
Pol-san, how was it today?
いやー、本当になんか今日も楽しい時間を過ごしたなーって感じですね！
Man, it really feels like I spent a fun time today too!
いや、1時間のような気がしないね。
Yeah, it doesn't feel like an hour.
そうですね。なんか2時間くらいなんかやった気もしますけどね。
Right. It feels like we did about two hours.
その言い方しちゃうとフブキ君、なんか違うんじゃないかな？
If you put it like that, Fubuki-kun, isn't that a bit off?
あ、そう、そうですかね？まあ、60分もやってますと...
Oh, is that so? Well, when you do 60 minutes...
あ、60分に感じる1時間！
Ah, one hour that feels like 60 minutes!
あ、そうですね！はい！
Ah, right! Yes!
え、じゃあこれ振るけど、鷹嶺ルイ、どうだった？これ今日、めちゃくちゃ忙しくなかった？
Well, I'll pass it to you, Takane Lui, how was it? Weren't you incredibly busy today?
え、何のことですか？
Eh, what are you talking about?
いや、色々分身してたけど。
No, I mean, you were splitting yourself up into many.
え、分身？いや、あ、違う...ごめんなさい、ごめん。
Eh, splitting? No, ah, no... sorry, sorry.
でもね、あの色んなアーティストの皆さんと共演ができて、とっても嬉しかったです。ありがとうございました！
But you know, I was very happy to be able to perform with various artists. Thank you very much!
おお！
Oh!
これ、そういえば今日、鷹嶺ルイ誕生日。
By the way, today is Takane Lui's birthday.
そうでしたね！はい！冒頭でも触れましたけども。
That's right! Yes! We mentioned it at the beginning too.
おめでとうございます！
Congratulations!
今更感あるんですけど、ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
It feels a bit late, but thank you! Thank you!
なんか言うてたよね。
You were saying something, right?
言うてた。/ そうそう。
We were. / Right, right.
今日はね、この後に...
Today, after this...
メンバーシップ限定でNGシーンの公開配信とかもありますので、
there'll be a membership-only stream showing NG scenes and such,
色々お話ししようかなと思います。
so I'm thinking of talking about various things there.
NGシーン？
NG scenes?
NGシーン見てない！NGないでしょ！
I haven't seen NG scenes! There aren't any, right?
NG、まあ先ほど私が出しましたけどね。
Well, I just made an NG earlier, didn't I?
そういうのを色々、ちょっと出していこうかなと思いますんで。
I'm planning to show various things like that.
ルイ君のファンは必見ですね。
Lui-kun's fans definitely shouldn't miss it.
メンバーシップの方もよろしくお願いします。
Please check out the membership too.
ぜひ見に来てください。
Please come and watch.
せっかくですので、ゲストの皆さんにも少し感想を聞いていきましょう。
Since they're here, let's hear some impressions from the guests.
まずは、いぬたかししらみさーん！
First, InuTakaShishiLamy!
ルイ姉、お誕生日...
Lui-nee, Happy...
...おめでとうー！
...Birthday!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
いぬたかししらみ、イエイイエイイエイ！
InuTakaShishiLamy, yay yay yay!
またゲームしましょうね。
Let's play games again.
しま、しましょうー！
Let's, let's do it!
はい、ありがとうございましたー。
Yes, thank you very much.
では続いて、あやめさんいかがでしたでしょうか。
Next, Ayame-san, how was it for you?
はい、ルイちゃん、お誕生日おめでとおお！
Yes, Lui-chan, Happy Birthday!
ありがとうだ余。ありがとうだ余。
Thank you-da yo. Thank you-da yo.
一緒に歌えて良かったんよ。
I'm glad we could sing together.
呼んでくれてありがとう。
Thank you for inviting me.
良かった。イエーイ！
I'm glad. Yay!
はい、ありがとうございました。
Yes, thank you very much.
なんか、とっても可愛かったですね。
That was very cute, wasn't it?
可愛かったですね。
It was cute.
では、本当にあっという間でございますが、
Well, it's really gone by in a flash,
今夜のミュージックガーデンはここまでとなります。ありがとうございました！
but tonight's Music Garden ends here. Thank you very much!
それでは、またどこかでお会いしましょう。さようならー！
Until we meet again somewhere. Goodbye!
さようならー！
Goodbye!
BIRTHDAY LIVE MUSIC GARDEN 2023.6.11.SUN 21:00 TAKANE LUI Birthday 2023